hostiserver.com 2019-05-25

# Privacy policy - HostiServer

This Privacy Policy only applies to this Website. It does not apply to any Websites that might be operated by Hostiserver’s clients or their clients. Hostiserver’s clients may or may not have their own privacy policy. If you have questions about a Hostiserver’s client's privacy policy you must contact that client directly. Hostiserver expressly denies any responsibility for any information that you provide to a Hostiserver client or a client of a Hostiserver client.

This Privacy Policy is an integral part of the Terms of Services which is incorporated herein by reference (<https://www.hostiserver.com/terms-of-service>).

If Subscribers use Services, we request personally identifiable information from them on our order form. Subscribers must provide contact information (such as name, email and mailing address) and financial information (such as credit card number, CVV and expiration date). During the purchase process, Subscribers may provide optional information to us. If that information is provided, it is covered by this Privacy Policy; however, providing it is voluntary.

## Our Commitment to Privacy

Hostiserver is committed to protecting the privacy of visitors to this Web site ("Site"). To accomplish this, we have implemented a comprehensive Privacy Policy that governs all information collected on or submitted to our Site. By accessing, browsing or using the Site, you acknowledge that you read, understand, and agree to the terms and conditions of Hostiserver’s Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, please do not access, browse, or use this Site.

## The Information We Collect and How We Use It

**Non-Personal and Aggregated Information.** When you visit our Site, we may log general data, such as your domain name (e.g., [www.Hostiserver.com](https://www.hostiserver.com/)), the name of the Web page from which you entered our Site, which pages you visit on our Site, and how much time you spend on each page. We use this information to continually monitor and improve our Site and for internal analysis. In particular, we use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Site, track Subscriber's movement, and gather information for aggregate use. (IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.)   
**Personal Information.** As a visitor to our Site, you may choose to use the Site to send us personal information (e.g., your name, mailing address, telephone number, and e-mail address); for example when you send a question via the Site, register for a particular service, or submit your resume through our Site. Anytime you submit personal information for a specific purpose using the Site, your information is used for that purpose only unless you consent otherwise or as required by law.

When you submit personal information to Hostiserver on this Site, you understand and agree that this information may be transferred across national boundaries and may be stored and processed in another country, which may not provide privacy protections similar to those your country provides.  
We do not send unsolicited e-mail to you or other visitors to our Site. We use e-mail to respond to e-mail messages from you, to confirm product or service orders placed online and to engage other communication that you have authorized or that we have determined necessary to more effectively service you and our customers.

We do not intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13.

In many cases, you choose the amount of information you supply (e.g., when sending us information through the Site, you may choose to include only an e-mail address and not a telephone number or mailing address for replies). There may be instances where some of the information that we ask you to provide is identified as mandatory and some as voluntary. In such cases, if you do not provide mandatory personal information with respect to a particular activity, you will not be able to engage in that activity.

**We may collect the following additional data about each user:**  
1\. Date and time of:  
\- most recent successful and unsuccessful authentication  
\- last change of password  
2\. Number of good logins and failed attempts.  
3\. Your most recent passwords - to make sure you follow the prevailing security policy regarding password re-use.  

When you login and / or change your password, we may record further information in log files, such as the IP address used, in line with the purposes stated above. This information can help in following up any doubtful activity relating to your account. It will not be used to monitor your activity, except to allow the removal of the account when no longer used.

## Cookies and tracking technologies

The term "cookie" refers to files that are transferred from a Web site to your computer's hard drive.. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information that Subscribers submit while on our site.

HOSTISERVER uses cookies to allow you to log in ans access to different pages of our Services without re-entering your email address and password.

If Subscribers reject cookies, the site may no longer be used.

## Log files

HOSTISERVER gathers certain information automatically and stores it in log files. This information includes Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

## Visitors to our website

HOSTISERVER’s web servers collect information from visitors to the website linked to this Privacy Policy. Because each Subscriber’s computer and browser configurations are different, we may collect some, or all, of the following information during their visit:  
\- Internet protocol address;  
\- The type of browser or computer used;  
\- The number of links clicked within HOSTISERVER’s website;  
\- The state or country from which our website was accessed;  
\- The date and time of visit;  
\- The name of Internet service provider used to access our website;  
\- The web page visited prior to coming to our website;  
\- The pages viewed on HOSTISERVER’s website.  
We use this information to improve our website, services and Subscriber experience, as well as communicate with Subscribers. 

## Who We Share It With

By registering yourself, you authorise the disclosure of the details you have entered in the user registration system to any Hostiserver site that you access after having given your email address and password. If you were registered by your organisation, your consent is assumed to have been given (implicitly or explicitly) for the transfer of your details.

We may share non-personal, aggregated information with our customers, partners, and advertisers. Aggregated information is not linked to any personal information that can identify an individual person or Website.

Unless we have your permission or are required by law, we only share the personal information you provide through our Site with Hostiserver affiliates and/or business partners that are acting on our behalf. We make every reasonable effort to ensure that such Hostiserver affiliates and business partners, including those in the U.S. and/or any other countries, protect your personal information consistent with our Privacy Policy.

HOSTISERVER will not divulge your information to third parties with the following exceptions:  
\- the duly authorised support unit or help desk responsible for the domain in which you are registered; \- the duly authorised sales or account manager who is authorized to conduct negotiations with you and enter into binding contract with you with repsect to any existing or future Services. 

## Data retention

We will retain Subscriber’s information for as long as their account is active or as needed to provide Subscribers services. If Subscribers wish to cancel their account or request that we no longer use their information to provide them services, contact us at [support@hostiserver.com](mailto:support@hostiserver.com). We will retain and use Subscriber information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Following termination of the Subscribers’ agreement with us, Subscribers will have no access to this information, and we may delete it for any reason, at any time.

## Our Commitment to Data Security

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect through the Site. However, please be advised that Hostiserver cannot and does not guarantee and has no control over the public or third party network through which you send your personal information to Hostiserver’s Site.

## Our Commitment to Children's Privacy

Protecting the privacy of children is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our Site from those we actually know are under 13 years of age, and no part of our Site is structured to attract anyone under the age of 13.

## Linked Internet Web Sites

This Site provides hyperlinks that, when clicked, take you to another place within the document, to another document altogether, or to other Web sites not controlled by Hostiserver. These hyper-linked Web sites may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided herein. Hostiserver is not responsible for the collection, use or disclosure of information collected through these Web sites, and Hostiserver expressly disclaims any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

## How to Correct, Amend, or Delete Your Information

We honor requests from you to correct or amend your account information (for example, your name, address, or billing information). This excludes information that is only held in log files: if you wish to access your log file entries, you may request it by writing. You may verify that appropriate corrections have been made. To correct or amend account information, contact [support@hostiserver.com](mailto:support@hostiserver.com). To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

A response will be given within a period of six weeks from the date of receipt of the request.

However, if your details were registered through a third party, this may not be possible and you will have to contact that third party in order to have the information changed.

Since all technical data is collected automatically, it is not possible to modify any of the technical data held by the authentication service, with the exception of the password itself.

## Privacy Policy Changes

This Privacy Policy is subject to change. Any changes to Hostiserver’s Privacy Policy will be posted on the Site. All information submitted through the Site to Hostiserver is subject to the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, as amended.

## How to Contact Us

Should you have other questions or concerns about Hostiserver’s Privacy Policy, please contact us at [support@hostiserver.com](mailto:support@hostiserver.com).
